tigerdroppings.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - 8/2/12 | TigerDroppings.com

Your privacy is important to us. To protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our privacy practices and the ways your information is collected and used. 

This notice applies to all information collected from users or submitted by users on our website. If you are a user of our website, including those users in the European Union (EU) Area, your continued use of the website signifies your consent to the information collection, our privacy policy and our terms of use. If you do not consent and are a user from the EU Area, then you should discontinue use of our website until we are able to provide an opt-out mechanism relating to the collection of personal information. 

Personal information collected by us includes, but is not limited to: 

* Email Address (for registered users only)   
* IP Address (for all users) 

We do not share your email address or IP address with outside parties. This information is used by the moderators of the website to facilitate quality control and to communicate with you as necessary. 

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures intended to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may collect and use, among other data, non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit [networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at tigerdroppings@gmail.com.
